const info = {
  1609040898: {
    subject: 'Bitcoin',
    potSize: '20',
    totalWinners: '0',
    killerQuestion: '1',
    potPerWinner: '20',
    paymentMethod: 'Monero',
    paymentMethodIcon: 'eye-off',
    actualSlideLink: '',
    notesLink: 'https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1UOjb-m9Gg6We9UNn_RtMWSGi1IWhCNPAMD1mTbB2JDg/edit?usp=sharing',
    summary: `This was my first show and I only had one contestant. The platform worked liked a beauty, but I just have to get more contestants.
    You can view the gameshow info below and see how you would have fared in this show. I will be sweetening the pot to 100 usd and coming with some more great questions.`,
    questions: {
      hv: {
        question: 'What Crypto Subject would you want to learn about?'
      },
      1: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'What controls bitcoin that you own?',
          options: ['Government', 'Private Key', 'Exchanges', 'Bitcoin Developers']
        },
        answer: '1'
      },
      2: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'Bitcoin is really good at having...',
          options: ['Privacy', 'Flexibility', 'Government Approval', 'Security']
        },
        answer: '3'
      },
      3: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'The Creator of Bitcoin was...',
          options: ['Satoshi Nakamoto', 'Bill Gates', 'Vitalik Buterin', 'Elon Musk']
        },
        answer: '0'
      },
      4: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'The Bitcoin Whitepaper was released',
          options: ['2010', '2008', '2007', '2006']
        },
        answer: '1'
      },
      5: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'The Max Number of Bitcoin that can ever be made is:',
          options: ['30 Million', '21 Million', '1 Trillion', '32 Million']
        },
        answer: '1'
      },
      6: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'Mt. ____ was the name of a major exchange that was hacked.',
          options: ['Bit', 'Kraken', 'Gox', 'Makalu']
        },
        answer: '2'
      },
      7: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'A Proof of Work method cited in the Bitcoin White Paper is:',
          options: ['Encrypt Cash', 'Bullet Cash', 'Fast Cash', 'Hash Cash']
        },
        answer: '3'
      },
      8: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'The first commercial hardware wallet released was:',
          options: ['Ledger', 'Trezor', 'Bitbox', 'Coldcard']
        },
        answer: '1'
      },
      9: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'The database that a caused an accidental Bitcoin Fork was:',
          options: ['Mongo DB', 'Level DB', 'Berkeley DB', 'Mysql DB']
        },
        answer: '2'
      },
      10: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'Segwit discounts Witness Data by a factor of:',
          options: ['8', '4', '6', '12']
        },
        answer: '1'
      }
    }
  },
  1610672400: {
    subject: 'Bitcoin Security',
    potSize: '100',
    totalWinners: '0',
    killerQuestion: '1',
    potPerWinner: '20',
    paymentMethod: 'Bitcoin',
    paymentMethodIcon: 'eye-off',
    notesLink: 'https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1u418hPBQpO5MCFUpSMfvTFa-2jvsUaBGSnpCKnbWdgc/edit#slide=id.gb31904321e_0_76',
    summary: `This show had some good info about Bitcoin Security in order to help people 
    keep thier bitcoib gains.`,
    questions: {
      hv: {
        question: 'What about Bitcoin Security Would you like to learn?'
      },
      1: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'A Commong Phrase in Crypto is: Not your ____, not your coin.',
          options: ['Government', 'Exchange', 'Passwords', 'Keys']
        },
        answer: '3'
      },
      2: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'Coinbase Insures __% of their crypto?',
          options: ['2', '0', '75', '100']
        },
        answer: '0'
      },
      3: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: '_____ is non-custodial P2P decentralized Bitcoin and cryptocurrency exchange',
          options: ['Exodus', 'Bisq', 'Binance', 'Electrum']
        },
        answer: '1'
      },
      4: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: '____ is a type of social engineering attack were someone disguises themselves a trustworthy entity',
          options: ['Phishing', 'Exploit', 'Ransom Attack', 'Switcheroo']
        },
        answer: '0'
      },
      5: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'Which hardware wallet brand lacks a secure element? ',
          options: ['Bitbox', 'Coldcard', 'Ledger', 'Trezor']
        },
        answer: '3'
      },
      6: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'Which hardware wallet does not use code from trezor in their firmware github?',
          options: ['Open Dime', 'Coldcard', 'Keep Key', 'Blockstream Jade']
        },
        answer: '3'
      },
      7: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'A 15 year old crypto researcher that found exploits in Ledger products:',
          options: ['Alena Vranova', 'Eric Larchevêque', 'Saleem Rashid', 'Andrew Chow']
        },
        answer: '2'
      },
      8: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'The max number of keys in a “standard” p2sh multisig transaction as stated in bitcoin core is:',
          options: ['5', '10', '15', '20']
        },
        answer: '2'
      },
      9: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: '_____ secret sharing is way to split up your mnemonic',
          options: ['Hardened', 'Rivest', 'Split', 'Shamir']
        },
        answer: '3'
      },
      10: {
        questionInfo: {
          question: 'Hal Finney’s Bcflick used ____ to improve wallet security.',
          options: ['Trusted Computing', 'Split Computing', 'Trustless Computing', 'Timed Computing']
        },
        answer: '0'
      }
    }
  }
}
exports.default = info
